README.md 5/15/2020

Marco Lackovic



Resume

- Last update 15-May-2020
- Download the latest version in PDF

Bio

Software engineer with 5 years of software development experience in the industry, 7 years in the academia as research fellow and teaching assistant. EESTEC alumni. Born and raised in Italy, relocated to Estonia in 2015.

Languages

- Italian: native speaker
- English: fluent
- Estonian: intermediate (B1)
- · Croatian: elementary

Work Experience

Full stack developer

- GrabCAD, 2019 → present
 - o Domain: 3D modeling community management
 - o User base: millions world
 - Tech stack: ruby, rails, rspec, sidekiq, redis, vuejs2, angularjs, elasticsearch, postgresql-10, git, github, docker, markdown
 - o Tools: windows, wsl, rubymine, visual-studio-code, tortoisegit, jenkins, slack, jira
- GrabCAD, 2018 → 2019, 1 year
 - Domain: 3D printing order management
 - User base: hundreds world

README.md 5/15/2020

• Tech stack: node.js, npm, typescript, reactjs, semantic-ui, graphql, jest, enzyme, apollo, typeorm, postgresql-10, express, git, github, docker, kubernetes, markdown

- Tools: windows, visual-studio-code, tortoisegit, teamcity, slack, jira
- Helmes, 2016 → 2018, 2 years and 10 months
 - Domain: Mobile phone repair management
 - User base: thousands Northern Europe
 - Tech stack: asp.net-mvc, C#, angularjs, javascript, yarn, bootstrap, rest, iis-express, sql-server, bitbucket, git
 - Tools: windows, visual-studio-2015, visual-studio-2017, rider, octopus, postman, slack, jira, confluence, ssms, tortoisegit
- Helmes, 2015, 10 months
 - O Domain: Healthcare
 - User base: hundreds Estonia
 - Tech stack: webforms, C#, soap, javascript, bootstrap, telerik, sql-server
 - Tools: windows, visual-studio-2008, visual-studio-2012, ssms

Research fellow

- UNICAL, 2011 → 2015, 4 years: Distributed Data Mining, Grid Computing
 - Tech stack: java, globus-toolkit, soap, web-services, latex
 - Tools: linux, eclipse

Teaching assistant

- UNICAL, 2007 → 2015, 8 years: Object Oriented Programming, Multi-Threading Programming
 - Tech stack: java, c++
 - Tools: linux, eclipse, libreoffice

Education

- UNICAL 2011: PhD in Computer Engineering
- UNICAL 2007: Master in Computer Engineering

Links

- Stackoverflow
- LinkedIn
- Google Scholar

README.md 5/15/2020

GitHub

- Profile
- Contributions